♪ We ♪
♪ Are the crystal ♪
♪ Gems ♪
♪ We'll always save the day ♪
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way ♪
♪ That's why the people ♪
♪ Of this world ♪
♪ Believe in ♪
♪ Garnet ♪
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst ♪
Pearl: ♪ And pearl ♪
And Steven!
这儿又有一个!
Here's another one!
知道了,史蒂文!准备...
Got it, Steven!Ready...
走你!
Go!
-抓住它的腿!-那不是个腿!
-Grab its legs!-That's not a leg!
嗷!
Ow!
想想挺瘆人的
It's a little disturbing that
铁石英一直把这些堕转的宝石关在笼子里
Jasper was just keeping these corrupted gems in cages.
我们不是正在这样做吗
Isn't that what we're doing?
有所不同
That's different.
她们在泡泡的稳定环境中被呵护着
They're cared for in the stasis of the bubble.
只要她们还在泡泡里，就伤害不了其他人--
As long as they're bubbled,they can't hurt anyone --
她们也不会受苦
and they won't suffer.
这就是玫瑰所期望的
It's what Rose wanted.
哈，我想这就是最后一个了
Huh. I guess this is the last of 'em.
真不敢相信这些蠢东西以前是宝石人!
I can't believe these dumb things used to be gems!
珍珠，紫晶，准备好
Pearl, Amethyst,get ready.
这只很容易受惊
This one is flighty.
母星上堕转的宝石不是这样的吗?
Are corrupted gems not like this on homeworld?
母星上没有堕转的宝石这种东西
We don't have anything like this on homeworld.
走起
Here we go.
石榴!
Garnet!
简直太糟糕!
That was terrible!
看起来容易做起来难!
This is harder than it looks,you know!
你们怎么能都被那东西耍了?
How could you all be outsmarted by that thing?
这个，第一点，它从石榴身上跑了过去
Well, first,it ran over Garnet,
然后紫晶试着用--
and then Amethyst tried to use her --
呃，咱们不需要实况转播
Uh, we don't need the play by play.
人总会犯错的--即便你能看到未来
Mistakes happen -- even when
you can see the future.
对啊，橄榄，来看看你能做成什么样
Yeah, Peridot.Let's see you do better.
这个嘛，我从铁石英手上救下了你们
Well, I saved all your butts from Jasper.
我想我能帮上你们这个忙
I suppose I could help you here, too.
随你便
Feel free.
多么好的机会来炫耀下我的金属能力!
This'll be a great chance to show off my metal powers!
我们的工作已经完成了
Then our work here is done.
呃，我，我想...
Uh, I-I'm...
你真的打算帮她?
Are you seriously going to help her?
这个...
It's just...
她在这儿独自一个，不知道她会做什么
she's all alone out here,with no idea what she's doing.
别担心，橄榄石没事的
Oh, Peridot will be fine.
我是怕怪物出事!
I meant the monster!
好吧
Okay.
想呆多长时间都行
Take as long as you need.
呃，石榴，你确定?
Uh, Garnet, are you sure?
等我!
Wait!
她们派你接我回去?
Did the others ask you to bring me back?
不，我是来帮忙的!
No, I came to help!
通常我们是一起出动才能抓宝石怪的
It usually takes all of us to capture a corrupted gem.
那是因为你们试着和宝石怪拼蛮力
That's because you try to out-brute it.
我们来和它拼脑力!
We're going to outsmart it!
所以...我能帮忙吗
So...I can help?
我倒是可以借鉴下你的打怪经验
I could use your experience dealing with these things.
但这根本不公平
It just doesn't seem fair.
此话怎讲
Why's that?
你和我组队之后
With you and me teaming up,
那东西根本没机会逃跑
that thing won't stand a chance.
棒!
Yeah!
跟上它!
After it!
它在干嘛?
What's it doing?
也许它喜欢闪亮的玩意?
Maybe it likes
shiny things?
简直完美!
This is perfect!
我刚想到一个完美的橄榄计划!
I've just concocted a flawless Peri-plan!
你的橄.计.是啥?
So what's the P.P.?
如果我用我的金属能力
If I use my metal powers,
整个东西都会砸在怪物身上!
the whole thing will fall onto the monster!
试试看!
Give it a try!
慢慢地...
Carefully...
它...没掉下来
It's...not falling.
也许需要拆掉另一条腿
Maybe another leg needs to go.
掉啊!
Fall!
你这蠢...
You stupid...
哦，简直了!
Oh, come on!
快掉啊!
Fall already!
橄榄石!小心!NPeridot, watch out!
哦对，谢谢提醒
Oh, right.Thank you.
呃，橄榄石!
Uh, Peridot!
它在那!抓住它!
There it is!Get it!
继续分散它注意力!我来干掉它!
Keep distracting it!I'll finish it off!
你还好吗
You okay?
我想我们该...
I think we need to...
调整下战略
revise our strategy.
你准备好听第二个橄榄主意了吗?
Are you ready for the second Peri-plan?
第一个不是特别好啊
The first one wasn't so great.
是的，我已经知道了，史蒂文
Yes, noted, Steven.
但是这个主意更加完美无瑕!
But this plan is even more flawless!
我拆掉了注入器做成了一门简易大炮!
I cannibalized the injector to make a rudimentary cannon!
注意看
Observe.
哇!震撼!
Whoa! Impressive!
确实如此
You got that right.
用这个方法，我们可以远距离干掉它!
This way, we can take it out from a distance!
哦，它在那!
Oh, there it is!
放着我来!
I got it!
呵，你个土块儿
Heh, you clod.
哈?
Huh?
发射啊，你这傻--
Work, you stupid --
呃...嘿
Uh...hey.
这轮算你赢好了
You win this round.
好
Okay.
我分析了下前两个橄榄计划的问题
I've analyzed the problems with the previous two Peri-plans.
依靠注入器的方案引入了
Relying on the injectors introduced
太多的复杂变量
too many complicating variables.
现在我们只需用简单的物理!
Now we only have to rely on simple physics!
我们等到它走到我们正下方
We'll wait until it gets right up under us,
趁它没有防备--因为它傻到不会有戒心
not suspecting a thing --because it's so dumb!
那时我们就扔下这块石头，砸它的脑袋!
And then we'll drop this rock on its stupid head!
简直更完美无瑕!
It's even more flawless!
而且在这个高度，没有啥能砸到我们了!
And at this height,nothing can fall on us!
但是如果它不停在我们想要的地方呢?
What if it doesn't stop where we want it to?
我已经尽力了，史蒂文!
I'm doing the best I can,Steven!
我--
I--
我觉得--
I think --
你身子还真结实呢，对吧
You don't poof easily,huh?
我们橄榄石比看起来结实多了
Us Peridots are tougher than we look!
棒!
Yes!
这肯定能成，这绝对完美!
This is going to work.This is going to be perfect!
这将会是...
This is going to be...
在浪费时间...
a waste of my time.
为啥我一直成功不了?
Why can't I master this?
哦，橄榄石，没关系的
Aw, Peridot, it's okay.
即使你的橄榄计划一个也没成功
Even if none of your Peri-plans worked,
至少都很欢乐啊
at least they were really funny.
她们也会这么想的
The others will probably think so, too,
我们回去告诉她们
when we go back and get 'em.
回去?
Go back?
我要向世界宣布，我，橄榄石，绝不前进
Let it be known that I, Peridot,refuse to move forward --
或者后退--直至成功为止
or back --until I am victorious.
好吧
Right.
我搞不懂
I don't get it.
我比一般橄榄石要聪明
I'm smarter than your average Peridot.
为什么今天败北于一只机能退化的
How did I fail today against some barely functional,
愚蠢，土块儿似的，蠢怪兽?
stupid,cloddy, dumb-dumb?!
嘿，嘿，堕转宝石可不傻
Hey, hey, corruptions aren't dumb.
它们只是思维方式不同罢了
They just think a little different, that's all.
等下，先确认下我的地球词汇
Okay, just to make sure my Earth vocabulary
是正确的...假设，我是个怪物
is correct on this...let's say I'm a monster.
假设我一天到晚都在用脸砸地
I spend all my time slamming my face into hard objects
然后向天上吐舌头找乐子
and throwing my tongues in the air for fun.
你不管这叫...蠢?
How am I not...dumb?
这个，她至少会做一些正确的事吧
Well, she must be doing something right.
你看到现在都没中你的橄榄圈套
She hasn't fallen for any of your Peri-plans.
纯属侥幸!
It's luck!
那玩意做不了任何有逻辑的事!
Nothing that thing does makes any sense!
嘿
Hey.
你为啥用你的松软甜蜜小石头砸我?!
Why are you bombarding me with your confectionery puff rocks?!
让你感受下怪物的痛苦!
To show you what it's like to be a monster!
想象我是个看到你就尖叫的吓破胆的人类!
Pretend I'm a freaked-out human screaming at you in fear!
想象我是个野生地球动物
Pretend I'm an Earth animal chasing you
追你追到无处可躲
away from your first safe hiding spot!
想象我是个想把你蒸发掉的绿色宝石人!
Pretend I'm an angry green gem trying to poof you!
这就是你目前的生活--
This is life for you now --
无尽的苦难!
endless suffering!
-看!你明白了没?-什么
-There! You see?-Yeah.
你现在做的一切都很合逻辑了
What you're doing makes total sense.
你记不记得你当时什么感受
You remember what it was like
那时候你珍视的一切都被夺走
to have everything important taken away?
被攻击?被包围?
Being under attack?Feeling trapped?
你当时很沮丧!她现在也一样!
You were frustrated.So is she!
为什么试着不换个角度看待这些事
Why don't you try thinking about all of this
从她的角度看
from her point of view?
嗯
Hmm.
你能做到的
You can do it.
呃
Ugh.
这只脏兮兮的甩舌头的家伙面前根本认真不起来
I can't take this dirty tongue-flapper seriously.
像...怪物一样...思考
Think...like...a monster.
Blap!
嗷
Aw.
嘿!
Hey!
没事的，我们不是来打架的
It's okay!We don't want to fight!
让橄榄石包住你就好
Just let Peridot bubble you!
我们会相处很好--
We can all get along --
不不不不不!
No, no, no, no, no!
给我...你的...宝石!
Give me...that...gem!
橄榄石!
Peridot!
我成功了
I did it.
哦，嘿，你们回来了!
Oh, hey, you're back!
呃，其实我们根本就没走
Eh, we never really left.
就知道你俩会很搞笑的
We knew it'd be funny.
预知能力
Future vision.
你们...你们一直以来都在看?
You...you were all watching this whole time?
我就说我能做到的
I told you I could do it.
但是我也要承认，比我想象的要难
But I have to admit, it was more difficult than expected.
这只堕转宝石真的值得我倾尽全力
This corrupted gem was truly an adversary worthy of my skill.
哇，橄榄石!
Whoa! Peridot!
很棒的泡泡，橄榄!
Nice bubble, Peri!
我-我应该怎么做
W-What do I do with it?
发送出去
Send it off.
拍一下顶端
Just tap the top.
旅途愉快!
Happy trails!
所以说它送去哪了?
So, where did it go?
家
Home.